<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tours on Xfce Desktop Environment</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tours on Xfce Desktop Environment</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.10 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.10/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to new major features of Xfce 4.10. It only covers the visual part of what has been done; for the full list of changes, see the Xfce 4.10 changelog .&#xA;Online Documentation During the 4.10 development we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to remove user manuals from the packages and move them to an online wiki at &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://docs.xfce.org&amp;quot;&amp;gt;docs.xfce.org. The reason for this change is to make &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://docs.xfce.org/wiki/documentation&amp;quot;&amp;gt;contributing and updating the documentation easier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.12 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.12/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to new major features of Xfce 4.12. It only covers improvements made on the surface; for the full list of changes, see the Xfce 4.12 changelog .&#xA;Window Manager (xfwm4) Window Switcher Dialog The window manager&amp;rsquo;s Alt+Tab dialog is now fully themeable and also gained two new modes: a &amp;lsquo;List&amp;rsquo; mode and a &amp;lsquo;Window Preview&amp;rsquo; mode. Furthermore users use their mouse to click/select the window they want to give focus to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.14 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.14/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to new major features of Xfce 4.14. It only covers improvements made on the surface; for the full list of changes, see the Xfce 4.14 changelog .&#xA;Settings Manager (xfce4-settings) Color Profiles Dialog A new dialog for setting color profiles for monitors, printers and scanners was introduced. It acts as a frontend to various daemons that talk directly to colord, e.g. saned (scanners), cupsd (printers) or xiccd (monitors).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.16 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.16/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to new major features of Xfce 4.16. It only covers improvements made on the (user-visible) surface; for the full list of changes, see the Xfce 4.16 changelog Visual identity: New icons and palette In order to make Xfce shine a little more out of the box and to strengthen its visual identity we created new icons for all of our core applications and based them on a shared palette to ensure consistency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.18 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.18/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to new major features of Xfce 4.18. It only covers improvements made on the (user-visible) surface.&#xA;Check the full Xfce 4.18 changelog for a detailed list of changes.&#xA;Widget Library (libxfce4ui) Filename Input Dialog XfceFilenameInput is a comfortable widget for filename input, which was added in order to prevent invalid filenames at an early stage and to give detailed feedback on the concrete problem.&#xA;XfceFilenameInput - trailing whitespaces XfceFilenameInput - slash Generic Shortcut Editor This widget is a shortcut editor which was introduced in order to have a graphical interface to modify component-specific shortcuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.4. tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.4/</guid>
      <description>As of today, the long awaited version 4.4.0 of the Xfce Desktop Environment is finally available. I will try to highlight some of the new features which have been added since the last stable release.&#xA;Desktop Icons One of the most often requested features during the 4.0 and 4.2 was support for icons on the desktop. Now, with Xfce 4.4.0, this feature was finally added to the desktop manager Xfdesktop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.6 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.6/</guid>
      <description>The long awaited 4.6.0 version of the Xfce Desktop Environment is finally available. We will try to highlight some of the new features which have been added since the last stable release.&#xA;Desktop Manager (xfdesktop) Since desktop icons have been introduced in Xfce 4.4, people have expressed the need to allow the selection of multiple icons (rubber banding). With Xfce 4.6, the Xfdesktop manager finally implements this feature: you can select multiple icons, remove them, etcetera&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xfce 4.8 tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tour/4.8/</guid>
      <description>This tour will introduce you to all the new major visual features in Xfce 4.8. This is only the visual part of what has been done; for a full list of changes, see the Xfce 4.8 changelog .&#xA;File Manager (thunar) Remote shares browsing Thunar now has optional support for GVFS which will allow you to browse remote shares using Thunar: FTP, Windows Shares, WebDav and SSH servers&amp;hellip;&#xA;Thunar browsing a remote share New file operations progress dialog When several file operations (copy or move) are being handled in parallel, Thunar now shows a single progress dialog which displays all the relevant information.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
